sava here's an onion this piece it won't
сава вот э лучок этот кусок он не
bite off with your teeth you won't be able to bite it off
откусится зубами ты не сможешь его
you won't be able to bite it off
откусить ты не сможешь его откусить
thinly sliced ​​it so it melts just lard you
тоненько нарезал чтобы таяло просто сало
see yeah
видишь угу
show me he bit off something he bit off it's
покажи он что-то откусил же откусил
cool
прикольно
almost Vova
вообще почти вовка
this happens when you eat Bushy's legs
такое бывает когда ножки буши
chances chances you have to
хаваешь шансы шансы
lower it like that I can't do that I can't do that how did you give birth like
надо ещё так опустить я так не могу я
that split
так не могу как ты так рожу раскол
me who fed me up like that
меня кто так
not who fed me up but how did you
раскормил вот не кто раскормил а как
feed me up how did you feed me up that lard is one but
раскормил как раскормил что сало едини а
show me you eat this lard what can you
покажи ты жрёшь это сало что можно
eat wait in lard here's an onion well I wo
кушать подожди в сало вот э лучок ну я
n't show you now everything is there show me how
тебе не покажу сейчас всё там покажи как
it is and how can you eat lard with onions
оно и как можно сало с луком есть с
eat with onions with your mouth well how does it not
луком есть ртом ну как бы оно же не
bite lard how do you show me I don't believe that you
кусается сало как покажи я не верю что
can bite off lard it doesn't bite you have it's hard
можно откусить сало не кусается у тебя
lard I once
пода оно твёрдое сало я когда-то в
tried it as a child it's very hard it's
детстве пробовал оно очень твёрдое его
not like that  bite off the lard me I mean
так не откусишь сало меня в смысле
when I was a kid lard wait what have I
когда-то в детстве сало подожди ты что
always said with pride that lard
я всегда говорил с гордостью что сал -
is a Ukrainian product I am not Ukrainian
это украинский продукт я не украинец
Ukrainian I am a Jew
украинец я еврей
wait I have always said and defended
погоди я всегда говорил и отстаивал
I am a Jew we do not eat lard at all you understand
я еврей мы сало не едим вообще понимаешь
I do not believe that you can bite off lard like
я не верю что можно сало откусить вот
that it does not bite off it is hard what do
так оно не откусывается оно ж твёрдое
you mean well if of course you tore off a leg from a pig
ты что ну если ты конечно ляшку от свини
you of course well this piece it will
оторвал ты конечно ну вот этот кусок он
not bite off with your teeth
не откусится зубами
you will not be able to bite it off you will not be able to bite it off I
ты не сможешь его откусить ты не сможешь
cut it thinly so that it melts
его откусить тоненько нарезал чтобы
just well this is what I cut it will
таяло просто ну вот это то что нарезал
not bite off did
оно не откусится
you manage to see it or something well show me
ты его разглядеть успел что ли ну покажи
how you can bite it off just take a
как его можно откусить вот просто возьми
piece take a piece take a bite it is
кусок откуси кусок откуси это
impossible well it seems to me it will be
невозможно ну мне кажется это будет
disgusting that I will yes why disgusting well it is
противно что я буду да почему противно
ok just show it ok you
ну нормально просто покажи нормально ты
will not chew it just having taken a
же не будешь пережёвывать просто
bite
откусива
you understand now a Ukrainian is talking to me
ты понимаешь мне сейчас украинец говорит
about lard you well I am not Ukrainian I am a
про сало ты вот ну я не украинец я
Jew we eat lard we do not  we eat lard
еврей едим сало мы не едим сало
no well I honestly feel sorry for you I mean you
не ну мне честно тебя жалко в смысле ты
don't eat lard or what you eat lard the Torah
сало не ешь что ли ты едим сало нам тора
forbids us
запрещает
show me show me what you can bite off just
покажи покажи что можно откусить просто
show me I don't believe that lard it bites
покажи я не верю что сало оно
off I once
откусывается я когда-то его ножом
tried to cut it with a knife like it's hard rest the
пробовал разрезать типа про оно твёрдое
head of a pig bite off its
на свинью отрестите голову откусить ей
ear well show me show me a piece here's a small
ухо ну покажи покажи кусок вот маленький
piece take a bite I don't believe that it
кусочек откуси я не верю что оно
bites off it cuts barely it's hard
откусывает оно режется еле-еле оно ж
lard lard you I mean lard is
твёрдое сало сало ты в смысле сало
hard you what I saw once I had a
твёрдое ты что я видел когда-то у меня
Ukrainian friend you he showed him
знакомый украинец был тебе он показывал
he couldn't bite off I cut it barely
он не мог откусить я отрезал еле-еле
cut it with a fork held it and
отрезал вилкой придерживал и ножом
cut it with a knife cut it with a knife man man
отрезал ножом отрезал мужик мужик вот
look I have a question for you you
смотри у меня такой вопрос тебе ты
see my I see well can you argue with my
вижу ну ты разве поспоришь с моими
gastronomic tastes inclinations no so I
гастрономическими вкусами наклонностями
believe that you eat fat yes but
что нет так я верю что ты ешь жир да но
you're not lard you don't bite off lard
ты не сало сало ты не откусываешь разве
unless  you cut it into small pieces
что ты её на маленькие кусочки порежешь
and what do you do with this lard you lick it
а что ты с этим салом делаешь то лижешь
like you probably cut it into pieces and
как ты его наверное режешь по кусочкам и
then eat it in small pieces
тогда уже съедаешь кусочками маленькими
too damn yeah you would have already if it was
тоже блин да ты бы уже если бы оно
bitten off you would have already shown it once and
откусывалось ты бы уже раз показал и всё
it would have bitten off you probably won't be able to bite it off it
оно откусилось бы ты не сможешь откусить
probably doesn't bite off for 5 minutes you
его наверное на откусывает 5 минут
probably need to tighten it up well tell
подтягивать наверное надо хорошо скажи
me what is your real Ukrainian lard
мне вот ваше настоящее украинское сало
like in general I'm not Ukrainian I'm Jewish
как оно вообще вот я не украинец я еврей
and what do you have listen come on look come on
а что у те слушай давай так смотри давай
if you show me that this
если ты да покажешь мне что это
lard really bites off I'll say
действительно сало откусывается я скажу
Zelensky
зеленский
no well I you can without lard tied up
не ну я те ты можешь без сал связал
[ __ ]
[__]
you traded the president for a piece of lard well like so that it would be so that like
ты президента на кусок сала променял ну
you did
типа вот чтоб было ну чтоб типа ты
something and I did something come on
что-то и я что-то сделал давай
what yes what am I answering you yes if you
чего да что я тебе отвечаю да если ты
show that this lard really
покажешь что это действительно сало
bites off I'll say that
откусывается я скажу что
Zelensky you'll cut the lard I don't have any more
зеленский сальцо порёшь у меня больше
cut off this
нет вот от этого отрежь
and you want him to cut off a small one
а ты хочешь чтобы он маленький отрезал
not here  the one that
не вот тот который
was what are you saying
был что говоришь
he will now prepare some
он сейчас подготовит тебе какой-то
specially cut off for you yes yes I say:
специально отрезанный да да я говорю:
"cut the lard" well cut it well cut
"нарежь сало" а ну нарежь а ну нарежь
it and he says: "I won't cut it" well
его а он говорит: "не нарежу" ну нарежь
cut it it's small once you cut it all off it can't
ты это ж маленький раз отрезал всё оно
even be cut you
же даже нарезаться не может видишь
see you see you know what guys we've
видишь ты знаешь в чём ребят мы его
eaten it almost everything there's nothing left to
сожрали почти уже всё всё нечего
cut - make one look here is
резать-то больше сделай один смотри вот
this piece that you showed is there or has he already eaten it he's already
этот кусочек что ты показывал есть или
eaten it well we've
он сожрал уже он сожрал его уже
eaten it all you'll cut one small one and
ну всё съели нарешь один маленький и
show that it bites off I'll tell you
покажи что он откусится я скажу тебе
Dasha Zelensky Zelensky
даша зеленский зеленский
oh well so why do you need it why well come on I
о ну и так зачем тебе почему ну давай я
admit I'm from Ukraine I admit it lard
признаю я из украины я это признаю сало
and Zelensky it doesn't belong to anything at all come on
и зеленский он вообще ни к чему не
exchange Zelensky for lard
относится давай променяй зеленского на
come on bite off a piece bite off a piece lard
сало давай откуси кусок откуси кусок
is lard look bite off this piece
сало - это сало смотри откуси этот кусок
show that it bites off and I'll say I'll
покажи что он откусывается и я скажу я
say like this  bit off some
скажу вот так вот откусила
fat see yeah
сало видишь угу
show me he bit off something zhi bit off cool
покажи он что-то откусил жи откусил
cool
прикольно прикольно
he also has an onion yeah yeah and there's another
он ещё лук угу угу и вон ещё
onion he still won't believe the
лук он всё равно не поверит
previous one for some reason he's angry at us he doesn't believe
предпрошм он почему-то обозлённый на нас
what he wrote you can bite off
он не верит что писал можно откусить
maybe no I didn't believe I didn't believe why are
может нет я не верил не верил а почему
you laughing tell us the truth wait I
ты угораешь скажи нам правду подожди я
have to say yeah look Zelensky will
же должен сказать да смотри зеленский
destroy you okay
вас уничтожит
come on come on well
ну и ладно давай давай ну
hello how are you
здравствуйте как у вас дела вы откуда
guys where are you from Moscow and where are you going I'm from the city of
ребят москва а вы куда я из города
Khmelnitsky are you from Moscow itself or from the
хмельницкий вы из самой москвы или из
region from Moscow itself right here in the center we are
области из самой москвы вот в центре мы
right in the center now.sa were you born
сейчас прямо в центре.са это вы родились
there or did you come here yeah were you born were born on
там или приехали да родились родились на
Vykhin were born understood what you talk about
выхин родились понял о чём общаетесь
differently how are you in
по-разному как вот у вас настроение
general how is life super I heard that
вообще как живётся супер я слышал что
there were drones flying into the Moscow region the other day
там было на днях прилёты дронов в
that's true and oh
московскую область это правда а о
right in the Moscow region but damn it's
правильно в московскую область но блин
not clear at all in Domodedovo in the residential building
вообще непонятно в домодедово по дому
here is the airport just suspended work
вот аэропорт только приостановил работу
question: why not on the airport but on the
вопрос: почему не по аэропорту а по
residential building well probably he was flying to the
жилому дому ну наверное он летел в
airport but the Russians
аэропорт але но там же россияне
installed these rebs there that jam the
поставили эти рэбы которые глушат
signals and they reject you s that they were
сигналы и они отклоняют ты сь что они по
flying on starlink yes there rap doesn't work no no no no no no
старлинку летели да там рэп не робит не
rap works I tell you as a person who is now engaged in them yeah rap works you fpv
занимается угу рэп работает у тебя fpv
drone mavic can catch when if
дрон mavic может поймать когда если у
you have satellite communication rap won't
тебя спутниковая связь рэп у тебя не
close for you listen did you ever see a starlink station
закроет слушай ты видел когда-то станцию
yes
да у
what size is it here so that you do
нас какая она по размерам во вот чтоб те
n't and it was on this airplane yes
не и она стояла на этом на самолётике да
no are you kidding you
нет ты что на приколе у тебя же связь
also have satellite communication maybe starlink
ещё спутниковая может быть starlink -
is a system that you have directly
это система которая у тебя напрямую есть
this if let's go so this airplane
это если давай так вот этот самолётик
that flew to Domodedovo so you know
который летел на домодедова так знаеш
how it works tell me well
как работает расскажи
you have a system portable
ну вот у тебя есть система переносная
station right so I have
станция правильно так вот у меня есть
starlink so yes I bought starling for myself
старлин так да вот купил старлинг себе у
through it you have internet at any
тебя через него есть интернет в любой
point essentially right right
точке по сути правильно
right no not quite  well, being
ну правильно нет не совсем ну находясь
under the satellite, well, tell me, well,
под спутником
come on, well, everything is correct, that
так ну расска ну давай ну всё верно то
is, this big receiver should
есть вот этот большой приёмник должен
fly the most huge one, this is the
лететь самой огромный вот такой это
third or fourth Starlin, this is it, so it
третий или четвёртый старлин вот такой
should, it should be
он так так он должен он должен быть
mounted on the plane, really, no,
монтирован на самолёте правда нет
but how does the plane work, the plane does not
а как как самолёт получается самолёт не
distribute the Internet, it has enough
раздаёт интернет ему хватает принятия
signal reception, do you know how a UAV works, well,
сигнала ты знаешь как устроен бпла
tell me, so it receives a
а ну расскажи мне так он принимает
signal, a Starlink signal receiver, where did
сигнал приёмник сигнала старлинка откуда
it get the
у него
receiver, well, most likely, it was originally
приёмник ну скорее всего изначально уже
made in it, and I don’t take my words back, are you
сделан в нём а не беру слова обратно вы
serious about Baba Egu, go to Baba Egu,
его серьёзно ити на бабу
and yeah, look, uncle, what are you talking about, a completely
а да ну смотри дядь без вы что вообще
stupid,
наглухая
cool topic, here’s Baba Yaga, Baba Yaga, I
прикольная тема вот на бабу ягу на бабу
believe in Babagu, maybe it’s super,
ягу верю на бабагу может быть да супер
listen to yourself, no, you should have a
слушай себе вот вообще нет у вас должен
reception, like any drone
быть приём как бы любой беспилотник
works the same way as the American ones and
работает так же как и американские и
ours, with Baba Ega, with Babaega, I believe yes, its
наши с баба егой с бабаегой верю да её
carrying capacity is just logical, yes,
грузоподъёмность как раз логично да
let’s say how it works, and wait, and Baba
допустим как работает и подожди и баба
Baba Iga works at short distances
баба ига работает на коротких дистанциях
there on the front where it is and where you have
там на фронте там где есть а где у вас
yes on the territory of Russia starling
да на территории россии старлинг
works on the territory of the Moscow
работает на территории московской
region
области
yes it shouldn't
да не должен
but although wait wait we turned on the day before yesterday we had
а хотя стой подожди мы позавчера
wi-fi we
включали у нас wi-fi-то был
launched this for fun they
мы ради прикола запускали эту нам
brought us when the new fourth but it's
привезли когда новый четвёртый но он
smaller by the way well there is a bypass there
меньше кстати ну там есть обход там всё
anyway so and so there is no bypass and in the fact
равно так и так там не в обходе а в том
that
что
as I will ban in Ukraine but I will not
как я запрещу на украине но я не буду
ban in Ukraine it is prohibited but at the same time
запрещать на украи запрещено но при этом
it is also somehow satellite TV will be like this well
это также как-то спутниковое тв будет
in theory I can
такой ну я же по идее могу спутниковое
connect Ukrainian satellite TV in Moscow I can
тв украинское подключить в москве могу
let's do this you connected to the satellite
давай так ты подключался к спутниковому
Internet starlink through
интернету starlink через
what chat show on the TV show on the
что чатик покажи на теле покажи на
phone the starling application and I myself
телефоне приложуху старлин а я что сам
connected not I will just tell you that
подключал не я тебе просто скажу что
yes yes yes and that
дадада
is and how do you think they flew
а то есть а как по-твоему они долетели
so well
так
as
ну как
Ukrainian know-how
ноу-хау украинское
as well as your know-how our
так же как ваше ноухауть наше
fiberglass
стекловолокно
and what will you do for us
да и что вы нам сделаете
I like well look we  we sli your
мне нравится ну смотри мы мы сли вашу
idea with fiber optics and yours yes
идею с оптоволокном и ваших да
found listen what question
нашло слушай какой вопрос
also look also you first of all the Iranians
также смотри также вы сначала у иранцев
idea with the martyrs we appreciated and now about
идею с шахедами мы оценили и теперь по
Domodedovo and everything look started with the fact that
домодедова и всё смотри началось с того
you in short about Ukraine yes with your
что вы короче по украине да своими этими
uh drones now we including the
ээ бплашками теперь мы в том числе и
Moscow region you can't do anything
московской области вы ничего не можете
yes now we had flights not
сделать да теперь у нас прилёты были не
on residential buildings no here we have just on
по жилым домам нет вот у нас как раз по
residential buildings but look Ukrainian
жилым домам а смотри украинские
drones hit accurately yes
беспилотники бьют чётко да
oil refinery
нефтеперерабатывающий завод
oil refinery where you in
нефтеперерабатывающий завод там где вы в
Moscow decided to push this air defense
москве решили натолкать этого пво
which rap yes which jams that's where it
которое рэп да которая глушит вот там
flew into the houses you yourself are to blame no need to
полетело в дома сами виноваты не нужно
jam it you need to let it reach the
глушить нужно пусть он долетает до
plane a second you didn't do anything peaceful give me give me
самолёта секунду вы нели по мирном дай
one question I'll ask one question yes
дай вопрос один задам один вопрос да вот
look you say that everything is so good the
смотри ты говоришь что всё так хорошо
system is
система
there but what is the situation on the front now I
там а какая ситуация на фронте сейчас
have no idea me me head
понятия не имею меня меня гла
at all if Moscow is being bombed look at you
вообще если москву бомбят смотри у тебя
your Moscow is being bombed yes you  you see you're not at the front, yes, in
москву твою бомбят да ты же не на фронте
short,
видишь ты сидишь да твою страну короче
your country is being bombed, yes, your country is being bombed, yes, and you're
бомбят да твою страну короче да а вы
sitting here and in short, damn, you're scratching yourself, yes,
сидите тут и короче блин чухаетесь да
why didn't you why didn't you go defend
да почему ты почему ты не пошёл защищать
your country, NATO is bombing your Moscow
свою страну нато бомбит вашу московскую
region, residential buildings, residential buildings, Adolf, you
область жилые дома жилые дома адольф ты
I want to talk to a smart guy, he's smart,
я с умным хочу поговорить вот он умный
that's how it should be, I'll talk to a smart guy, look,
вот так надо я с умным поговорю смотри
smart guy, why can't you defend
умный да почему вы не можете защитить
your nine-story buildings, yes, we're taking on your
свои девятиэтажки да мы берём и по вашим
nine-story buildings, and we want to and we can, and what are you going to
девятиэтажкам хотим и можем и что вы
do, what are you going to do, Adolf, decide, this is Adolf, this is it,
сделаете что ты адольф реши это адольф
and you're okay,
вот этот а ты нормально
can you explain why, explain why
можно объясни почему объясни почему
Russia is not Adolf, not I'm talking to Sanek, I'm
россия не адольф не я с саньком говорю я
like Adolf, I'm not talking to you, look,
типа адольф я с тобой не говорю смотри
Bel, I'm talking to you, what's your name, Bel,
бел я с тобой общаюсь как тебя зовут бел
wait, Bel, what's your name, I'm Bil, what's your name, his name is
чекай подожди бел как тебя зовут меня
not mine, call
бил как тебя зовут его не меня зови
Adolf, what's your name, can you be more
адольф как тебя зовут
respectful, well, I just
а можно поуважительней ну как я просто
want to know your name, to be more respectful, catch
имя хочу узнать чтобы поуважительней
Chubatovasi, what's your name,
поиме чубатоваси как имя у тебя
his name is Oleg, what's your name, Olezhik
его олег зовут как у тебя имя олежик
tell me what is your name olezhik
скажи как у тебя как тебя зовут олежик
if you want you can call him sanok
если хочешь можешь его саньком называть
it's short if because of the last name what is your
это коротко если из-за фамили как тебя
name let's have a
зовут давай чтобы мы с тобой пообщались
normal conversation oleg oleg yes look oleg here
нормально олег олег да смотри олег вот
uh oleg tell me so why can't russia yes a
ээ олег скажи мне так почему россия да
great powerful country can't defend
великая могучая страна не может защитить
its nine-story buildings can't shoot down these
свои девятиэтажки не может сбить эти
drones somewhere when they fly out of
бпла где-то когда они вылетают из
ukraine why do they wait for it to fly over
украины почему ждут чтобы он пролетел
half of russia and a nine-story building so that people
пол россии и девятиэтажую чтобы люди
why can I ask one question how many
почему а можно один вопрос сколько всего
drones flew out and how many
вылетело беспилотников и сколько
flew I have no idea I don't know I'm
долетело я понятия не имею я не знаю я
not a mathematician but why can't russia
не математик но почему россия не может
defend itself why can't russia
защититься почему почему россия не может
hit some
орешником ударить по какому-то
zelensky with a nut and that's it and stop the war
зеленскому и всё и прекратить войну
why is it suffering I regret it
почему она страдает я об этом жалею
because
потому что
look I watched the video and the guy from
смотри я смотрел видео да мужик из
domodedovo says: "we I'm in my underwear he's in his
домодедова говорит: "мы я в трусах он в
underwear uh standing on the street I
трусах ээ стоит на улице я в трусах
ran out in my underwear because it exploded" and
выбежал потому что так взорвалось" да
mommy screams: "why are we simple
мамочка кричит: "за что мы простые
peaceful  people we show the video please"
мирные люди мы прокажи видео пожалуйста"
wait can I ask you one more question already
подожди а можно один вопрос ещё ты уже
yes don't ask allow don't
да не спрашивай разрешайте не
ask permission everyone ok ok
спрашивайте разрешения каждый хорошо
look yes it's streaming yes it's logical on
хорошо смотри да он стриминго да логично
the contrary I like it
наоборот мне нравится
look I want to ask such a question you
смотри хочу задать такой вопрос вот ты
said why I'm not at the front because it is
говорил почему я не на фронте потому что
necessary to protect yes that's clear just
нужно защищать да это понятно ты просто
explain to me why Russia can't
объясни мне почему россия не может
look why Russia can't protect
смотри почему россия не может защитить
a nine-story building one nine-story building in
девятиэтажку одну девятиэтажку в
Domodedovo why why can a
домодедово почему почему может пролететь
Ukrainian drone fly through all regions across the
украинский дрон через все области через
border it is not shot down in Bryansk it is not shot down in Oryol it is
границу его не сбивают в брянской его не
not shot down in
сбивают в орловской его не сбивают в
Kaluga and it arrives in Domodedovo
калужской и он прилетает в домодедово
why
почему
look answer my question no no you
смотри ответь на мой вопрос нет нет ты
now we will figure it out no I will not let you
сейчас мы разберёмся с этим нет я тебя
go no come on Adolf go
не отпущу нет давай адольф иди кофе
make some coffee for Oleg let's have a normal
сделай олежке давай пока чтобы нормально
conversation with Oleg yes in short let me
пообщались мы с олегом да короче давай я
talk to Oleg and have you seen how many
с олегом поговорю а ты видел сколько
Russian drones have flown across Ukraine that's
долетало дронов русских по украине так
clear yes Ukraine is a small
это понятно да украина маленькая
country - it is  in general i don't understand
государство- это вообще я не понимаю
why you still haven't destroyed
почему вы до сих пор не уничтожили
ukraine haven't bombed the banking sector yes you
украину не разбомбили банковую да вы не
can't and ukraine just goes and makes
можете а украина берёт и делает у себя
drones and launches them at nine-story buildings stupidly
дроны и запускает по девятиэтажкам тупо
Zelensky brazenly goes and says: "we
зеленский нагло берёт и говорит: "мы
will fly and bomb" fly and bomb that's
будем лететь и бомбить" лететь и бомбить
right well three yes that is killed yes
правильно ну три да то есть убила да
shot down yes already three dead there are where
изсбила да уже трёх дох есть там где
mirotorg was yes in the parking lot three
мироторг был да на стоянке три
three three with you know for you these are not
трое трое с понимаешь для вас это не
lives they don't matter yes but i'm not saying
жизни не важны они да а не говорю что
why can't you protect how many
почему вы не можете защитить сколько
must suffer this is already more than the
должны страдать это уже больше чем
residents of donbass died in twenty-
жителей донбасса погибло в двадцать
first do you
первом
know and you called me and then
до понимаешь и ты назвал меня а ты тогда
who are you defending your country no look
кто е защищаешь свою страну нет смотри
now you're running away from the answer because
ты сейчас убегаешь от ответа потому что
you don't want to say why your
ты не хочешь сказать почему твоя
country yes can't protect peaceful
страна да не может защитить мирных
residents grandmothers yes they must give birth out of fear
жителей бабушек да они должны рожать с
yes in these nine-story buildings yes
перепугу да в этих девятиэтажках да
why can't it because you
почему она не может потому что вы
really are a
реально
state you don't have where is your nut tree
государство у вас нету где ваш орешник
why not in Kyiv we really Zelensky
почему не по киеву мы реально зеленский
says you you are not with us  in Kyiv he
говорит вы вы не у нас по киеву прямо и
says directly: "and that's it" and there's nothing else in short
говорит: "и всё" и ничего короче нету
let's ban you too es na at the
давай мы ещё тебя забаним ес на на
end hello hello where are you from
концовочку здравствуйте здравствуйте вы
well from Russia and what do you talk about
ну с россии а чем общаетесь
yes so about that now here came up so
да так о том осём сейчас вот зашёл так
one such interesting question is there as I
вопрос один такой интересный есть я так
understand you are on the stream you have a lot of people
понимаю вы на стриме у вас много человек
probably someone will help answer I
наверное кто-то поможет ответить я вот
went to google maps I'm walking around Krivoy
зашёл на google карты гуляю по кривому
Rog now and noticed such a feature
рогу сейчас и заметил особенность такую
in construction in the roofs of
в строительстве в крышах
houses will you help me figure
домов поможете мне разобраться с
this out I'll switch the camera now
этом я сейчас камеру переключу
show and maybe you or someone else will answer
покажу и может вы или кто-то ещё ответит
why exactly such a triangle is needed
зачем вот именно такой треугольник нужен
on the
на
roof are you ready
крыше готовы
come on without these cameras explain again what's the
давай без этих камер объясни ещё раз в
joke to you in
чём тебе прикол
short I explain switch the camera
короче объясняю переключаю камеру
look you see there is a roof there is
смотрите вот видите есть крыша вот есть
such a triangle
вот такой треугольник
on top why is it needed and in all the houses
сверху зачем он нужен и во всех домах
here I'm walking around Krivoy Rog now
вот я сейчас по кривому рогу
generally everywhere this whole
гуляю вообще везде вот вся вот эта
story is why such a
история есть почему вот такой
triangle is hovering yes yes yes and it ah this is
треугольник витят да да да и она ах это
really in Krivoy Rog
реально в кривом роге
yes but it's not only in Krivoy Rog  horn I've
да но это не только в кривом роге это я
walked around so many places in Ukraine no no well
так много где в украине гулял да ну не а
show me somewhere else I don't believe it I'm
ну покажите ещё где-то я не верю я такое
seeing this for the first time how is this you'll show
впервые вижу как это это вы покажете
some Europe what kind of triangle we don't
какую-то европу какой треугольник у нас
have such triangles
нету таких треугольников
this is Krivoy Rog well that's for sure Krivoy Rog
это кривой рог ну вот точно кривой рог
it's Ukraine bn no in Ukraine in general there are
он украина бн нет по украине вообще
everywhere I'm interested in this question well for
везде есть меня этот вопрос
now show me another city
заинтересовал а ну пока другой город
with a triangle I'm interested for
покажите с треугольником мне интересно
example well have you seen the ornament on this
например а ну вы видели орнамент на этом
triangle what patterns are given there
треугольнике какие узоры там даются
not really well here's the
не особо ну вот
Petrovskaya region let's do it now
петровская область давайте так сейчас
load if Google has been there yet a little man
прогрузит если там ещё google человечек
about an incomprehensible task about a triangle of a
о непонятная задача о треугольник
triangle
триугла
well why is it even there well are there
ну зачем вот оно вообще есть ну есть
any suggestions now now
какие-то предположения сейчас сейчас
now show me show me let's
сейчас покажите покажите давайте
make it so the picture is clear
сделайте чтобы чёткая была картинка
show the triangles here like this you
покажите тут треугольники вот вот вот
see a triangle on the
такой же вот видите треугольник на на
roof triangle yes yes it's for
крыше треугольник да да это для
ventilation or what is it anyway why is this
вентиляции или что это вообще зачем это
necessary okay switch over I'll tell you tell me
надо ладно переключайся расскажу тебе
let's look according to the concept of the
давай значит смотри согласно концепции
organization of Ukrainian nationalists uh
организации украинских националистов ээ
uh such a concept was proposed by
ээ была такая концепция предложена
Roman Shukhevych yes uh one hut one
романом шухевичем да ээ одна хата одна
boivka is how to say in Russian one
боивка это как по-русски сказать один
house one fortress like that yeah that
дом одна крепость вот так как бы да то
is uh if you look old
есть ээ если ты посмотришь старые
fortification churches were also built with
фортификационные церкви строились тоже с
loopholes yeah these houses are also uh
бойницами да вот эти дома тоже ээ вот
like
как бы
made with a special strikha what is
сделаны со специальной стрихой что такое
strikha do you know what strikha is strikha is
стриха знаешь что такое стриха стриха -
up there strikha you can
это вот там наверху да стриха там можно
stuff a huge amount of weapons for
натолкать огромное количество оружия
example yeah and when like from sorry let's
например да и когда типа из извиняюсь
interrupt
перебьём
from the point of view of logic well like this
с точки зрения логики ну как бы этот
viewing is well there is no protection that is well why
просмотр есть ну защиты никакой то есть
mark weapons there that's not
ну зачем там оружие размечать так это не
protection the thing is that yes the head of the family
защита дело в том что да глава семьи
goes to the attic and from there shoots
выходит на чердак да и оттуда спуляет
wherever he wants yeah at all sorts of occupiers that is that
куда хочет да по всяким типа оккупантам
was the concept of the
вот то есть такая была концепция
organization of Ukrainian nationalists and
организации украинских националистов и
if you look yeah these
если вы посмотрите да то вот эти
triangles are present uh at
треугольники присутствуют ээ в самой
this very eastern point yeah that's in the city of
этой восточной точке да это ещё в городе
Rubizhne in the city of
рубежное в городе
Rubizhne in the Luhansk region uh there and in Russia there are
рубежное луганской области вот ээ там а
no more in Russia there are no more these
в россии уже нету в россии уже нету этих
triangles and it was these
треугольников вот и именно эти
triangles that they started making at the beginning of the 20th
треугольники начали делать в начале xx
century after  that in
века после того как в
venezov congress of the organization of
венезован конгресс организации
ukrainian nationalists was oun
украинских националистов было оун
created maybe you know there bandera shukhevych
создано может знаете там бандера шухевич
here this
вот этот
kanovaltsy so they decided that there
кановалец вот и постановили
will be let's
что будет
say the need to create partisan
скажем необходимость делать партизанские
detachments there will be the need to create an
отряды будет необходимость делать
underground ukrainian insurgent
подпольную украинскую повстанческую
army and if you look for example uh
армию и если вы посмотрите например ээ
for the sake of interest ivano-frankivsk region
ради интереса ивано-франковская область
verkhovyna this is the fruit of upa fruit of
верховина вот это оплод упа оплод
bandera yes there just yes there not
бандеровщины да там просто да там не то
that triangles there are high such
что треугольники там высокие прямо такие
triangles acute-angled so look for the
треуголь остроугольные вот посмотрите
sake of interest verkhovyna right now
ради интереса верховина прямо сейчас
verkhovyna yes verkhovyna verkhovyna
верховина да верховина верховина
ivano-frankivsk region there are
ивано-франковская область
small triangles such
там тут маленькие треугольники такие
isosceles yes oh equilateral and
равнобедренные да а ой равносторонние а
there are isosceles elongated like that
там прямо равнобедренные вытянутые вот
so verkhovyna this is for me approximately by the region to
так верховина это мне примерно по район
look because there I will look like this
смотреть потому там я так посмотрю такое
this is so verkhovyna
это так и есть верховина
ivano-frankivsk region not a small
ивано-франковская область не маленький
point well yes yes big
пункт ну да да большой
well now east or west will load
ну сейчас восток или запад прогрузится
so verkhovyna and there is not even a special street
так верховина а там даже особо улицы нет
something was on the
что-то было на
road verkhovy there stupidly  everything in the triangle
доро верхви там тупо всё в треугольнике
okay now it will load well well load
ладно сейчас грузанёт ну ну грузоните
look
посмотрите
because by the way in Ukraine the Internet costs
потому кстати в украине интернет стоит
if they
если они
have no idea yes because you
понятия не имею да потому что ты с
talked to Lithuania there 40 euros
литвой разговаривал там 40 евро говорит
for a month says it's
за месяц
expensive so Verkhovyna
дороговато так верхвина
loaded well here for now some
прогрузилась ну тут пока какая-то
incomprehensible location now I'll switch I'll even
непонятная локация сейчас переключу даже
show well some kind of like
покажу ну какая-то такая
either the Soviet Union or Europe
прямо то ли советский союз то ли европа
so let's go to the center let's Verkhovyna the
так давайте в центр давайте верховина
center
центр
Verkhovyna let's take a drink
верховина давайте возьмите напирту
turned on
врубил
no here it is up and you can see so here I
нет вот она вверх и видно так вот я
move this little man for example yes
этого человечка перемещаю например да
come on and here there is a central street
давай и тут вот есть центральная улица
some points come on come on there is a
какие-то точки давай давай давай там
bus station start from the bus station
автовокзал начинай с автовокзала вот
come to the bus station Verkhovyna
приди на автовокзал верховин
carefully he can see this now
осторожно он сейчас может это посмотреть
what shoot
что стрель
damn the
блин завис
man is hanging it seems like he is the man who
мужик походу его таки мужик который
was passing on the map shot
проходил на карте стрельнул
everything seems like in short
всё походу
Bandera supporters for two-hotels like that's
короче бандеровцы за двухсотели типа
it I'm looking at Krivoy Rog there are triangles
всё я смотрю кривой рог там треугольники
what kind of triangles are on the roof
что за треугольники на крыше
like subscribe comment and put
лайк подписка коммент и поставьте
write in the comment
напишите в комментарий
yes you or your friends had or have
да был или есть у вас или у ваших
such
знакомых такие
triangles subscribe to my instagram
треугольники підпишись на мій instagram
I don’t know what this is for, why else are
я не знаю для чго це тобі для чого ще
you there to marvel at
тобі там дивитись на
the rest for you, one two or three clicks
остле для тебе це один два або три клика
and you’ll follow me and I’ll say:
але ти птримаешь мене и я буду казати:
“wow, I have a lot of followers there and I
"вау в мене там купа фоловерів и в мене
’ll have a great
буде класний
mood, cool video” subscribe  on my
настро круті видео" підпишись на мій
instagram popik Andrey
instagram попик андрей
otak let me give you a check
отак давай я тебе очекаю